<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Port of Code</title>
    <link>http://cfaught.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Port of Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cfaught.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Javascript Basics</title>
      <link>http://cfaught.github.io/itemized/item1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cfaught.github.io/itemized/item1/</guid>
      <description>Javascript coming soon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>http://cfaught.github.io/posts/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 17:15:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cfaught.github.io/posts/test/</guid>
      <description> Hello World! Welcome to Port of Code, the place to learn programming! var s = &amp;quot;JavaScript syntax highlighting&amp;quot;; alert(s);  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing the ubuntu linux subsystem on windows 10</title>
      <link>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/installing_the_ubuntu_linux_subsystem_on_windows_10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/installing_the_ubuntu_linux_subsystem_on_windows_10/</guid>
      <description>I recently had the pleasure of restoring my Windows laptop after breaking something in a Linux dualboot (another story for another day). While going through all the process of setting things back up, I remembered that I had heard somewhere that Windows 10 now has the capability for developers to install a full Ubuntu environment within Windows (No Virtual Machine Required). This enables users to open a Bash shell and run Linux tools all without loading a VM or rebooting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Programming and Why is it Important</title>
      <link>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/what_is_programming_and_why_is_it_important/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/what_is_programming_and_why_is_it_important/</guid>
      <description>What is Programming? Before I get too deep into this, I want to talk a little bit about what programming is, what it is not, and why it is important in todays world. Programming is how we humans communicate specific instructions on how to do something to a computer. Programming is the tool that developers use to flesh out ideas for solving a problem. Unfortunately, computers require a very specific form of communication called a programming language.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I am Changing Careers to Software Development</title>
      <link>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/the_reason_for_weighing_anchor_and_setting_sail_with_software_development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/the_reason_for_weighing_anchor_and_setting_sail_with_software_development/</guid>
      <description>Some History In high school, I decided to take a class in Computer Science based in Java. At the time I was looking forward to making a game or something interesting, and was disenchanted when we delved into nothing but algorithims and data structures; I did, however learn a few things that would later become useful.
Fast forward a few years, in the summer of my sophmore year of college (2010), I started to read about people building interesting things with something called an Arduino which is a microcontroller programmed with a language based on C.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>