<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ruby on Port of Code</title>
    <link>http://cfaught.github.io/categories/ruby/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ruby on Port of Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cfaught.github.io/categories/ruby/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Programming and Why is it Important</title>
      <link>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/what_is_programming_and_why_is_it_important/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/what_is_programming_and_why_is_it_important/</guid>
      <description>What is Programming? Before I get too deep into the details on the topic of programming, I want to talk a little bit about what programming is, what it is not, and why it is important in todays world. Programming is how we humans communicate specific instructions on how to do something to a computer. Programming is the tool that developers use to flesh out ideas for solving a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I am Changing Careers to Software Development</title>
      <link>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/the_reason_for_weighing_anchor_and_setting_sail_with_software_development/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cfaught.github.io/blog/the_reason_for_weighing_anchor_and_setting_sail_with_software_development/</guid>
      <description>Some History In high school, I decided to take a class in Computer Science based in Java. At the time I was looking forward to making a game or something interesting, and was disenchanted when we delved into nothing but algorithims and data structures; I did, however learn a few things that would later become useful.
Fast forward a few years, in the summer of my sophmore year of college (2010), I started to read about people building interesting things with something called an Arduino which is a microcontroller programmed with a language based on C.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>